thank you very much for the fitting
person to inductee into the
International Hall of Fame considering
your history in Cleveland and all the
nationalities in our nearly 50 years of
friendship my congratulations to each of
my fellow deputies I think I've been to
all the induction is in when I was in
the audience I looked up there
I take uses and people all the feed this
hunter also like to recognize little
develop along the way starting to my
wife killing assistant county prosecutor
[Music]
our children Vicki who came all the way
to Florida recently heard her PhD in
economics or short sleeves and Danny's
way to run a cold they're still here
Danielle Chris and their daughter Mila
and David was ever represented
disease-filled in his overworld and my
brothers and sisters Tommy
Kenny Allen and his wife Regina
Ricky his wife Meredith especially my
sister Ginny was helping with everything
I and the family does for needs shawls
will it still be here as well and my
parents are elephant Lucy were both
deceased couldn't set a better example
for parents than any generation in many
cities the choristers
my alternate mothers my Westside mother
baby tomorrow
room has helped even almost everything
either political world with the
nationalist movements of volunteer
groups and without her or the public
wouldn't survive at 60 years in minutes
and my Eastside mother the team seats
when men that work with the board of
revision in 1984 79 who's been a mentor
to be for political civic
ever since and my church of over 70
years 70 lady blurts island by
immigrants over 130 years ago and now we
knew by immigrants represented today by
a dozen twisters headed by our pastor
for the spins
it was pleadings nationalities who
brought me through a successful career
from the various Czech organizations and
churches and especially the post Women's
Association that a longtime leader
Francis tensity
we're getting to be elected additionally
the council they there was Cleveland
ethics community asked me to brother
replacement retiring the kids Senate or
on the Cleveland school board to
represent the nationalities there's a
seven member board all the rest were
Democrats and twice the sorry she and
the entire American nationalist movement
the officers Valerie would appear to me
to the illness Terry McAuliffe and
attorney because dr. ruse who next
absolutely and my former law partner
mark Bill Miller the entire membership
misreport got me through my 13 years
services just Allegra Taylor I proudly
present of the nationalist movement
group with the started primarily by
people the people America from
oppressive totalitarian governments they
fled Nazi Germany in communist countries
behind the Iron Curtain during and after
the Second World War they came here for
the religious and personal freedom which
provided under national opportunity to
us terms of the guarantees of our
Constitution in an unusual move the
director Cecil B DeMille in the 1956
film The Ten Commandments team on stage
and spoke to the significance of the
story of Moses and Pharaoh said ladies
and gentlemen we have an unusual subject
the birth of freedom the story of Moses
the team in this picture is whether be
enough to be moved by God's laws whether
they are to be ruled by the whims of a
dictator like Ramses our men are
property of the state rather than three
schools under time the same battle
continues throughout the world today
later Ronald Reagan noted freedom is
never more
one generation away from extinction milk
pass it to our children in the
bloodstream it must be thoughtful
protected to pass time where we will
spend our sunset years colored our
children's children but it was lightly
United States had been words free so let
us not allow others to dictate when our
children learn and know of America and
Industry let's pass on the lessons of
freedom and opportunity of America and
its constitution to our future
generations so we don't have to again
learn the lessons of our country's
founding and the reasons people
undertook most hellish trips trips
during and after World War 2 to come to
America
[Applause]